// this is an example how advancestep.json need to be created , this is as simple as basic_steps.json file just for every question we need to add one more object called
//"tobeshown" it will have value 1 or 0 , 1 if want to show that question in advance mode and 0 if do not want to show that question in advance mode
// it is having one more thing different from basic_steps file the question which you want to show in advance will be given twice one time with "tobeshown"=0 and one with
//"tobeshown"=1 please scroll and observe 
[
    {
      stepName: "Identify Motion of objects",
      stepNumber: 1,
      stepQuestions: [
        {
          question: "How many moving objects are present?",
          options: [4, 6, 3, 1],
          answer: 2,
          threejsstep: "motion",
          threejssubstep: 0,
          threejssubsubstep: -1,
          show: ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083"],
          showfc: [],
          "tobeshown":1
        },
        {
          question: "How many strings are there?",
          options: [0, 1, 2, 4],
          answer: 2,
          threejsstep: "motion",
          threejssubstep: 1,
          threejssubsubstep: 0,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
          ],
          showfc: [],
          "tobeshown":1
        }
        
      ],
    },
    {
      stepName: "Write FBD equation for each Moving block",
      stepNumber: 2,
      stepQuestions: [
        {
            question:
              "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction",
            options: [
              "+30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
              "-30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
              "-30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
              "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            ],
            answer: 3,
            threejsstep: "fbd",
            threejssubstep: 1,
            threejssubsubstep: 100,
            show: [
              "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            ],
            "tobeshown":1
          },
        {
          question:
            "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings",
          options: [0, 1, 2, 3],
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 1,
          threejssubsubstep: -100,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
          ],
          answer: 1,
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the force at this point of intersection on red block?",
          options: ["T\u2081 upwards", "T\u2081 downwards"],
          answer: 0,
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 1,
          threejssubsubstep: 1,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
          ],
          showfc: ["Upward Forces T\u2081,", "Downward Forces "],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction",
          options: [
            "+30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "-30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "-30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
          ],
          answer: 3,
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 1,
          threejssubsubstep: 100,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
            question:
              "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction",
            options: [
              "+40+T\u2081+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
              "+40-T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
              "+40-T\u2081+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
              "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            ],
            answer: 3,
            threejsstep: "fbd",
            threejssubstep: 2,
            threejssubsubstep: 100,
            show: [
              "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
              "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            ],
            "tobeshown":1
          },
        {
          question:
            "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings",
          options: [0, 1, 2, 3],
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 2,
          threejssubsubstep: -100,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
          ],
          answer: 2,
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?",
          options: ["T\u2081 downwards", "T\u2081 upwards"],
          answer: 0,
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 2,
          threejssubsubstep: 1,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
          ],
          showfc: ["Upward Forces ", "Downward Forces T\u2081,"],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?",
          options: ["T\u2082 downwards", "T\u2082 upwards"],
          answer: 1,
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 2,
          threejssubsubstep: 2,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
          ],
          showfc: ["Upward Forces T\u2082,", "Downward Forces T\u2081,"],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction",
          options: [
            "+40+T\u2081+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+40-T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+40-T\u2081+T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
          ],
          answer: 3,
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 2,
          threejssubsubstep: 100,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
            question:
              "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the y-direction",
            options: [
              "+T\u2082+50=5.0a\u2083",
              "-T\u2082+50=5.0a\u2083",
              "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
              "-T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
            ],
            answer: 2,
            threejsstep: "fbd",
            threejssubstep: 3,
            threejssubsubstep: 100,
            show: [
              "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
              "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
              "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            ],
            "tobeshown":1
          },
        {
          question:
            "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for blue block cuts the strings",
          options: [0, 1, 2, 3],
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 3,
          threejssubsubstep: -100,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
          ],
          answer: 1,
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the force at this point of intersection on blue block?",
          options: ["T\u2082 downwards", "T\u2082 upwards"],
          answer: 1,
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 3,
          threejssubsubstep: 1,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
          ],
          showfc: ["Upward Forces T\u2082,", "Downward Forces "],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "Whats the FBD equation of blue block in the y-direction",
          options: [
            "+T\u2082+50=5.0a\u2083",
            "-T\u2082+50=5.0a\u2083",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
            "-T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
          ],
          answer: 2,
          threejsstep: "fbd",
          threejssubstep: 3,
          threejssubsubstep: 100,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
      ],
    },
   
    {
      stepName: "Constraint Equations",
      stepNumber: 3,
      stepQuestions: [
        {
            question: "What is the constraint equation for pink string?",
            options: [
              "+a\u2081+a\u2082=0",
              "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
              "-a\u2081+a\u2082=0",
              "-a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
            ],
            answer: 1,
            threejsstep: "constraint",
            threejssubstep: 1,
            threejssubsubstep: 300,
            show: [
              "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
              "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
              "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
              "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
            ],
            "tobeshown":1
          },
        {
          question:
            "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:",
          options: ["+a\u2081", "-a\u2081"],
          answer: 0,
          threejsstep: "constraint",
          threejssubstep: 1,
          threejssubsubstep: 1,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:",
          options: ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"],
          answer: 1,
          threejsstep: "constraint",
          threejssubstep: 1,
          threejssubsubstep: 2,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question: "What is the constraint equation for pink string?",
          options: [
            "+a\u2081+a\u2082=0",
            "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
            "-a\u2081+a\u2082=0",
            "-a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
          ],
          answer: 1,
          threejsstep: "constraint",
          threejssubstep: 1,
          threejssubsubstep: 300,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
            question: "What is the constraint equation for red string?",
            options: [
              "+a\u2082+a\u2083=0",
              "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0",
              "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0",
              "-a\u2082-a\u2083=0",
            ],
            answer: 1,
            threejsstep: "constraint",
            threejssubstep: 2,
            threejssubsubstep: 300,
            show: [
              "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
              "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
              "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
              "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
              "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
            ],
            "tobeshown":1
          },
        {
          question:
            "What is the number of parts which change length in the red string?",
          options: [5, 4, 2, 3],
          answer: 2,
          threejsstep: "constraint",
          threejssubstep: 2,
          threejssubsubstep: -1,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
            "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for red string:",
          options: ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"],
          answer: 0,
          threejsstep: "constraint",
          threejssubstep: 2,
          threejssubsubstep: 1,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
            "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for red string:",
          options: ["+a\u2083", "-a\u2083"],
          answer: 1,
          threejsstep: "constraint",
          threejssubstep: 3,
          threejssubsubstep: 2,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
            "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
        {
          question: "What is the constraint equation for red string?",
          options: [
            "+a\u2082+a\u2083=0",
            "+a\u2082-a\u2083=0",
            "-a\u2082+a\u2083=0",
            "-a\u2082-a\u2083=0",
          ],
          answer: 1,
          threejsstep: "constraint",
          threejssubstep: 2,
          threejssubsubstep: 300,
          show: [
            "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2083, T\u2081, T\u2082, ",
            "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081",
            "+40+T\u2081-T\u2082=4.0a\u2082",
            "+T\u2082-50=5.0a\u2083",
            "+a\u2081-a\u2082=0",
          ],
          "tobeshown":0
        },
      ],
    },
  ]
